+65 9859 4148







From B2B to B2C, I've designed web and mobile products as a product designer for 1.5 years, and recently coordinated B2B Enterprise products as a product manager with an array of experiences across functions like the product, marketing, design, agile and waterfall software development. I'm a highly-organised, collaborative team player who can fill any role as a generalist, and at the same time, dive deep into specific challenges. I'm currently a Computer Science sophomore at Goldsmiths, University of London.

Experience

Polymerize

Oct 2021 - Present, Product Manager

- Co-owned product with engineering and leadership team, managing backlog, documentation, testing, and complete product lifecycle
- Created, coordinated efforts for, and launched MVP for an Electronic Lab Notebook and self-managed Lab Inventory Management System in 6 weeks, working closely with leadership, engineering, and design team
- 3. Led design efforts for statistical prediction for experiment data feature in flagship product
- Established repeatable product requirements documentation practices to achieve an average handoff duration for designs of 4 days per document
- Led a product development team of 6, including 1 junior designer and 1 associate product manager, and fronted the creation of internal wikis for design, product, and research
- Spearheaded product team's inaugural product OKRs, experimented with implementing Agile company-wide, led design operations

Jul 2021 - Oct 2021, Product Designer

- 1. Designed and revamped company website in 1 month based on user interviews and research
- Sole designer for a product initiative to introduce statistic-based prediction to flagship product to close an MNC customer

GCL Asia

Jan 2021 - Jun 2021, UI/UX Designer

- Sole designer for and launched a B2B2C e-commerce web application with robust shop management systems in 4 months using Agile methodology
- 2. Designer for multiple projects, including an edtech web application and an e-commerce mobile application
- 3. Mentored a design intern and spearheaded internal design culture and practices
- Conducted remote user research for the Taiwan market for 3 different ideal customer profiles to iterate on web application

Anywhr

Jul 2020 - Dec 2020, UI/UX Design Intern

- 1. Designed for an internal itinerary booking platform and consumer-facing trip booking mobile application
- Spearheaded and conducted foundational user research into the travel market and traveller personas to iterate on a trip booking mobile application

Education

Oct 2020 - Present

Goldsmiths, University of London BSc (Hons) Computer Science (Web Development)

Web Development, Agile Software Development, Object-Oriented Programming, Algorithms & Data Structures

Apr 2015 - Apr 2018

Temasek Polytechnic **Diploma in Communications & Media Management**

Digital Marketing, Social Media Management, Graphic Design, Digital Animation

Skills

UI/UX

Figma, Balsamiq, Miro, Lucidchart, Adobe Illustrator, Dovetail, Mixpanel, Microsoft Clarity

Development

React, HTML5, CSS, ES6, Git Version Control, SQL, Firebase, NextJS, C++

Others

Asana, Airtable, Linear, Trello, Slack, Notion, Jira, Confluence, Google Analytics, Gitbook

Languages

English

Chinese (Simplified, Traditional)